A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Speeches, Series 33 FA372
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Van Nest Recreation Center Rally - Bronx, New York, October 18, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 3279)
- Anthony Amendola Wedding Reception, October 18, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 3280)
- United Nations Reception, October 19, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 3281)
- New York State Narcotic Addiction Control Commission Conference - Rochester, New York, October 19, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 3282)
- United Nations 25th Anniversary - New York State Theater Lincoln Center, October 19, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 3283)
- Women for Rockefeller: Plaza Hotel - New York City, October 20, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 3284)
- Javits, Goodell, etc. Rally, 22 West 55th Street, October 20, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 3285)
- Alfred E. Smith Memorial Foundation 25th Anniversary Dinner, October 21, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 3286)
- Association of Colleges and Universities - Dedication of Civic Center Campus, October 21, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 3287)
- Taxi Drivers Endorsement - New York City, October 21, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 3288)
- General Foods Tour - Westchester, New York, October 22, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 3289)
- Gabe Pressman's Communications Class Lecture: New School, October 22, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 3290)
- Readers Digest Tour - Westchester County, October 22, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 3291)
- Union Reception - Bohemia, New York, October 22, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 3292)
- Grade Crossing Elimination Ceremony, October 22, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 3293)
- St. John's University Dinner - New York City, October 22, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 3294)
- Syracuse Reception - Syracuse, New York, October 23, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 3295)
- Rev. O. D. Dempsey Endorsement, October 23, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 3296)
- Council on the Arts Press Conference - New York City, October 23, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 3297)
- Kelly, Hurley, Farley Endorsement, October 23, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 3298)
- Garment Center Rally - New York City, October 23, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 3299)
- Greenup/Baker Endorsement - New York City, October 23, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 3300)
- Jeff L. Greenup Endorsement, October 23, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 3301)
- Rockland County Rally Shoppers Paradise Shopping Center, October 24, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 3302)
- Democrats for Rockefeller Headquarters Visit - Queens, New York, October 24, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 3303)
- Weeklies for Rockefeller Dinner - Pocantico, New York, October 25, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 3304)
- Westchester Reception, October 24, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 3305)
- IRS Dedication - Brookhaven, Long Island, October 26, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 3306)
- Ministerial Inter-Faith Association - New York City, October 26, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 3307)
- Puerto Rican Leaders Breakfast, October 26, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 3308)
- Town of Brookhaven Republican Women's Club, October 26, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 3309)
- Business Men's Dinner - Port Jefferson, New York, October 26, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 3310)
- Contract Signing MTA: New Haven Railroad - New York City, October 27, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 3311)
- Jack Kemp Testimonial Dinner - Buffalo, New York, October 27, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 3312)
- Wall Street Rally, October 27, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 3313)
- Erie County Reception, October 27, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 3314)
- Radio Broadcast (Box 81, Folder 3315)
- Rabbis Endorsement - New York City, October 29, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 3316)
- Queens County Annual GOP Night Rally, October 28, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 3317)
- Nassau County Republican Rally, October 29, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 3318)
- Urban Development Corporation Event - Syracuse, New York, October 30, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 3319)
- Seneca Towers Dedication - Rochester, New York, October 30, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 3320)
- Watertown Airport Press Conference - Watertown, New York, October 30, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 3321)
- Utica (Oneida County) Reception - Utica, New York, October 30, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 3322)
- Oneida County Board of Legislators Reception - Whitesboro, New York, October 30, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 3323)
- White Papers: Aging (Box 81, Folder 3324)
- Agriculture - White Papers (Box 81, Folder 3325)
- White Papers: Arts and Culture (Box 81, Folder 3326)
- White Papers: Court (Box 81, Folder 3327)
- White Papers: Economic Growth (Box 81, Folder 3328)
- White Papers: Elementary Education (Box 81, Folder 3329)
- White Papers: Environment (Box 81, Folder 3330)
- White Papers: Federal-State-Local (Box 81, Folder 3331)
- White Papers: Health (Box 81, Folder 3332)
- White Papers: Higher Education (Box 81, Folder 3333)
- White Papers: Housing (Box 81, Folder 3334)
- Human Rights - White Papers (Box 81, Folder 3335)
- White Papers: Law Enforcement (Box 81, Folder 3336)
- White Papers: Mental Illness (Box 81, Folder 3337)
- White Papers: Mental Retardation (Box 81, Folder 3338)
- White Papers: Narcotics (Box 81, Folder 3339)
- White Papers: Parks and Recreation (Box 81, Folder 3340)
- White Papers: Power (Box 81, Folder 3341)
- White Papers: Social Service (Box 82, Folder 3342)
- White Papers: Transportation (Box 82, Folder 3343)
- Working People: White Papers (Box 82, Folder 3344)
- White Papers: Youth (Box 82, Folder 3345)
- Campaign Round-Up (Day Before Election), November 2, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 3346)
- Election Night Speech - Roosevelt Hotel, New York City, November 3, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 3347)
- Building Industries Employee's Association - New York City, November 20, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 3348)
- 90th Anniversary Convocation of the New York Board of Rabbis - New York City, December 1, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 3349)
- National Conference State Legislative Leaders - San Juan, Puerto Rico, December 1, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 3350)
- State Legislator's Meeting - San Juan, Puerto Rico, December 1, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 3351)
- Capital District Campaign Round-Up - Albany, New York, November 2, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 3352)
- Centennial Dinner YWCA - New York City, December 1, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 3353)
- Affirmative Action Agreement - New York City Building and Construction Industry 22 West 55th Street - New York City, December 10, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 3354)
- Citizen Union Searchlight Dinner, New York Hilton - New York City, December 8, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 3355)
- Housing Conference, December 10, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 3356)
- Urban Development Corporation (UDC) Press Conference UDC Office - New York City, December 10, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 3357)
- Testimonial Dinner in Honor of Mayor Edward J. Galvin - Albany, New York, December 10, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 3358)
- Affirmative Action Minority Agreement Press Conference - New York City, December 10, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 3359)
- County Chairman Meeting - Albany, New York, December 16, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 3360)
- Governor's Luncheon of the Finance and Advisory Committee of the State Safety Council - New York City, December 17, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 3361)
- Dinner for Senator Goodell, St. Regis Hotel - New York City, December 17, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 3362)
- Jewish National Fund Dinner, Honoring Rabbi H. Judah Hurwitz, December 17, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 3363)
- "Jeopardy" (Television Program) - New York City, December 18, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 3364)
- Opening Parker Dunn Memorial Bridge - Albany, New York, December 21, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 3365)
- Inaugural 1971, January 1971 (Box 82, Folder 3366)
- Inauguration of NAR for 4th Term, Assembly Chamber, State Capitol - Albany, New York, January 1, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 3367)
- NAR 4th Inauguration - Albany, New York, January 1, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 3368)
- Annual Message to the Legislature - Assembly Chamber - State Capitol, 12:30 p.m. - Albany, New York, January 6, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 3369)
- Reception for Lou Levine - New York City, January 13, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3370)
- Telephone Campaign Drop-In (T) Federation of Jewish Philanthropists, January 14, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3371)
- Young Israel "Man of the Year" Award Dinner - New York City, January 16, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3372)
- Mayor Lackey Dinner - Niagara Falls, New York, January 15, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3373)
- Governor Club Dinner, Plaza Hotel, 8:00 p.m. - New York City, January 18, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3374)
- New York State Association for Mental Health Annual Legislative Assembly Lunch, Sheraton - Albany, New York, January 26, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3375)
- Economic Club of New York, Waldorf Astoria Hotel, January 20, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3376)
- Annual Mayors Conference Meeting - Albany, New York, January 26, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3377)
- (T) Diamond Ball Drop-In, January 27, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3378)
- Second Panel Sheriff's Jury Annual Dinner, Hotel Baltimore (Cancelled) - New York City, January 27, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3379)
- Annual Westchester County Republican Dinner, Hotel Commodore - New York City, January 28, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3380)
- Joint Economic Committee, January 29, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3381)
- Federation of Women's Republican Club of New York State - New York City, January 29, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3382)
- Women's National Republican Club, Golden Anniversary Luncheon, Waldorf Astoria - New York City, January 30, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3383)
- American Legion 52nd Annual Legislative Dinner - Albany, New York, February 1, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3384)
- Miss Universe Luncheon - Albany, New York, February 2, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3385)
- Labor Leaders Dinner, Executive Mansion, February 2, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3386)
- National Press Club - Washington, DC, February 4, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3387)
- United Fund of Westchester Annual Dinner Meeting, February 5, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3388)
- Taping for Lincoln Day Dinner Tribute to Javits and Lefkowitz, February 8, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3389)
- New York State Builders Association - Albany, New York, February 8, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3390)
- New York State Association of Towns Luncheon (Drop-In) - New York City, February 9, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3391)
- Empire State Chamber of Commerce Legislative Dinner - Albany, New York, February 9, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3392)
- New York State Association of Fire Districts (Drop-In) - New York City, February 9, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3393)
- Business and Professional Women's Club, Red Room, February 15, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3394)
- Luncheon for Director of Empire State Chamber of Commerce, Mansion (Cancelled) - Albany, New York, February 10, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3395)
- Council of Elected Negro Democrats (Drop-In) - Albany, New York, February 10, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3396)
- New York State Publishers and Press Association Dinner, February 16, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3397)
- National Urban Coalition Dinner - Warrenton, Virginia, February 16, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3398)
- Revenue Sharing Day Press Conference, Red Room - Albany, New York, February 22, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3399)
- Commission on Children, Dr. Miller, 44 Holland Avenue - Albany, New York, February 22, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3400)
- Capitol Press Room Dinner - Albany, New York, February 22, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3401)
- Legislative Meeting of New York State American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Albany, New York, February 22, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3402)
- New York State Council of Churches Legislative Seminar, Red Room, Executive Chamber 5 p.m., March 1, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3403)
- "West Point Day" Proc. Sgng, Red Room 2:30 p.m., March 2, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3404)
- Press Conference Red Room, New York City Schools - New York City, March 2, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3405)
- Luncheon for National Association of Manufacturers (Revenue Sharing) (Cancelled), March 5, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3406)
- Legislative Pilots Association Dinner - Albany, New York, March 8, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3407)
- League of Women Voters Dinner - Albany, New York, March 9, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3408)
- 4-H Capital Day Red Room, 2:30 p.m., March 9, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3409)
- New York State Broadcasters Legislative Dinner - Albany, New York, March 9, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3410)
- Annual Rules Committee Dinner - Albany, New York, March 12, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3411)
- LCA, March 13, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3412)
- Testimonial Dinner in (1 p.m.) Honor of Wilma Rogalin (Sponsored by the Federation of Women's Republican Club, Thruway), March 13, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3413)
- Press Conference, Red Room Budget for Fiscal Year Starting April 1st, March 15, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3414)
- Friendly Sons of St. Patrick Dinner - New York City, March 17, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3415)
- United Jewish Appeal Inaugural Dinner - New York City, March 18, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3416)
- Albert Einstein College of Medicine Founders Dinner - New York City, March 21, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3417)
- Teen Age Republican (Drop-In) - Albany, New York, March 22, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3418)
- Patrolmen's Beneficial Association (Drop-In) - Albany, New York, March 30, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3419)
- Boyer Inauguration State University, Performing Arts Center, 2 p.m. - Albany, New York, April 6, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3420)
- Harvard Club - New York City, April 14, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3421)
- 100 Business Men Meeting - New York City, April 15, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3422)
- Drop-In Northeastern Regional Chairmen's Association of Republican National Committee - New York City, April 15, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3423)
- Harlem River Park Dedication - New York City, April 16, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3424)
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) National Legislative Conference - Washington, DC, April 19, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3425)
- Annual Luncheon of Associated Press - New York City, April 19, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3426)
- Bureau of Advertising of American Newspapers Publishers Association Dinner - New York City, April 20, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3427)
- Patriots Award Dinner - New York City, April 23, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3428)
- New York Conference of the African Episcopal Zion Church, April 26, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3429)
- Congress of Environmental Health - New York City, April 26, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3430)
- United States Congress of World Council of Churches - Albany, New York, April 27, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3431)
- Law Day Program Department of Law - Albany, New York, April 30, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3432)
- International Symposium on Public Employment Labor Relations - Albany, New York, May 4, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3433)
- Governor's Conference on Aging - New York City, May 7, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3434)
- Queens County Republican Reception - Long Island City, May 6, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3435)
- Department of Kodak Plant - Rochester, New York, May 6, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3436)
- Brazilian-American Chamber of Commerce Dinner - New York City, May 11, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3437)
- Council of Arts Awards - New York, May 15, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3438)
- Annual Dinner Business Committee for the Arts - New York City, May 17, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3439)
- Jewish Guild for the Bland - New York, May 17, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3440)
- Suffolk County Republican Committee - Huntington Station, New York, May 26, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3441)
- Reception for Labor - New York, June 2, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3442)
- Republican State Committee Luncheon - New York, June 10, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3443)
- New York Republican State Dinner - New York, June 10, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3444)
- 20th Anniversary of the Rome Air Dev. Center Griffis, June 11, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3445)
- Wright Park Manor - Ribbon Cutting 12 Noon - Rome, New York, June 11, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3446)
- Ways and Means Com. Panel - Washington, DC, June 15, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3447)
- Nassau County Republican Committee Garden City - New York, June 16, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3448)
- Senator Wagner Memorial Dinner, Scholastic Achievement Committee - New York City, June 16, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3449)
- Richmond County Chairman's Club Reception - Staten Island, New York, June 16, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3450)
- Presidential Visit - Rochester, New York, June 18, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3451)
- Empire Girls State 30th Anniversary Session, State University of New York Albany - Albany, New York, June 29, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3452)
- National Newspaper Association Convention - Rochester, New York, June 24, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3453)
- National Newspaper Association Convention - Rochester, New York, July 5, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3454)
- Senior Citizens Ground Breaking - Brooklyn, New York, July 15, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3455)
- Award Preservation New York Telephone Community Headquarters - New York City, July 21, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3456)
- New York State Building and Construction Trade Council Queensbury Hotel - Glens Falls, New York, July 22, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3457)
- National Tax Association Seminar - Washington, DC, July 23, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3458)
- Republican National Committee, July 23, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3459)
- Congressional Testimony on Water Pollution, July 28, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3460)
- Testimony - Committee on Government Operation - Washington, DC, July 29, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3461)
- Revenue Sharing Articles for Georgetown Law Review, July 29, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3462)
- Reception - Opening Labor College - New York, August 8, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3463)
- "Salute to Joseph M. Margiotta" 8 p.m. New York Hilton - New York City, August 11, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3464)
- New York State County Officers Association Annual Banquet, Concord Hotel 7:30 p.m. - Monticello, New York, August 16, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3465)
- International Downtown Executive Association - New York City, August 21, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3466)
- American Association of Motor Vehicle Administrators - New York City, August 21, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3467)
- Rockland County Breakfast, August 22, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3468)
- Sewage Treatment Plant Dedication - Haverstraw, New York, August 22, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3469)
- Associated Industrial Dinner - Lake Placid, New York, August 23, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3470)
- Dedication - New York State Bar Center - Albany, New York, August 24, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3471)
- Schyler Mansion Gardens - Albany, New York, August 24, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3472)
- Roswell Park Memorial Institute - Buffalo, New York, August 24, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3473)
- Long Island Association of Commerce and Industry, August 28, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3474)
- Route 17 Association Luncheon - Elmira, New York, August 29, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3475)
- Dedication Jamestown City Hall - Jamestown, New York, August 29, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3476)
- Press Conference on Community Development Art League of Women Voters, August 30, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3477)
- Columbus Citizen Committee - New York City, October 9, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3478)
- Knickerbocker Hospital - New York City, October 13, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3479)
- United Cerebral Palsy Association - New York City, October 14, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3480)
- Editors and Publishers Luncheon - Pocantico, New York, October 15, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3481)
- Association of New York State Life Insurance Companies - New York City, October 19, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3482)
- United Nations Association of the United States of America - New York City, October 19, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3483)
- Alfred E. Smith Dinner - New York City, October 20, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3484)
- Dedication International Paper Company - Ticonderoga, New York, October 21, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3485)
- Westchester County Association - Tarrytown, New York, October 21, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3486)
- Associated Industries of New York - Albany, New York, October 27, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3487)
- East River Transit Tunnel Tour and Press Conference 3:00 p.m. - Queens, New York, October 28, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3488)
- Utica Press Conference Oneida County Airport - Utica, New York, October 28, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3489)
- Syracuse Chamber of Commerce - Syracuse, New York, October 28, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3490)
- Press Conference - Defeat of Bond Issues, November 3, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3491)
- American Jewish Community Dinner - New York City, November 9, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3492)
- Republican State Committee (Kick-Off) Dinner - New York City, November 3, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3493)
- Governor's Conference on Alcohol Problems, Americana Hotel 10 a.m. - New York City, November 10, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3494)
- Association of Council Member and Colleagues Trustees Dinner - Syracuse, New York, November 12, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3495)
- Mary Switzer Service - New York City, November 15, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3496)
- State Traffic Safety Council Luncheon, November 16, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3497)
- State Park Dedication - Brookhaven, Long Island, New York, November 17, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3498)
- Environmental Workshop - Tarrytown, New York, November 20, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3499)
- New York State Psychiatric Institute 75th Anniversary Celebration (AM), Columbia University - New York City, November 22, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3500)
- New York State Commission for Children - New York City, November 23, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3501)
- Taft Institute Dinner - New York City, December 2, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3502)
- New York State Congressional Delegation and Representatives of State and Local Government Press Conference, St. Regis Hotel - New York City, December 3, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3503)
- State Bank of India Opening - New York City, December 8, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3504)
- Press Conference Tax Program - New York City, December 14, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3505)
- U Thant Tribute Luncheon - New York City, December 14, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3506)
- David Sarnoff - New York City, December 14, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3507)
- Wilbur Mills Meeting on Revenue Sharing, Red Room 2:15 p.m. Cancelled, December 15, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3508)
- Testimony Before Blantnik Committee - Washington, DC, December 9, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3509)
- No-Fault Press Conference - New York City, December 21, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3510)
- United Teachers Association Press Conference - New York City, December 27, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3511)
- Statement at Adjustment of Special Session of the Legislature State Capitol - Albany, New York, December 31, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 3512)
- Michigan's Fund Raising Dinner - Detroit, Michigan, January 6, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 3513)
- Albany Area of Chamber of Commerce - Albany, New York, January 11, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 3514)
- First Panel Sheriffs Jury Dinner - New York City, January 12, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 3515)
- Energy Conservation Workshop - Albany, New York, January 12, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 3516)
- Veterans of Foreign Wars Dinner (T) - Albany, New York, January 17, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 3517)
- County Officers Association Dinner (Cancelled) - Albany, New York, January 18, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 3518)
- Annual Message to the Legislature 1 p.m. - Albany, New York, January 18, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 3519)
- Gordon Howe Dinner - Rochester, New York, January 18, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 3520)
- Pocantico Hills School Groundbreaking - North Tarrytown, New York, January 23, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 3521)
- Vic Borella's Dinner - New York City, January 25, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 3522)
- Westchester County Dinner (Cancelled) 7 p.m. - New York City, January 27, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 3523)
- New York State Real Estate Board Banquet (Cancelled) - New York City, January 27, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 3524)
- New York American Legion Legislative Dinner (Cancelled) - Albany, New York, January 31, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 3525)
- Press Conference No-Fault Auto Insurance (Cancelled), February 1, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 3526)
- New York State Women's Legislative Forum - Albany, New York, February 1, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 3527)
- Empire State Chamber of Commerce Luncheon Mansion 12:30 p.m., February 2, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 3528)
- HR1 Testimony - Washington, DC, February 3, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 3529)
- Association of Fire Districts - New York City, February 3, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 3530)
- Association of Towns Luncheon - New York City, February 8, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 3531)
- Governor Club Dinner Dance, February 10, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 3532)